https://www.chicksaddlery.com/privacy-policy

New Horse Products
More...
Privacy Policy
Chick's is committed to providing the highest level of security and privacy regarding the collection and use of our customer's
personal information, as well as that of all visitors to our website.
Personal information may be collected through the submission of account
applications and online transactions. A detailed description of Chick's
Online Privacy is provided below. If you have additional questions regarding
the privacy of your personal information, please contact us.
Respect of Right to Privacy
Chick's respects your right to privacy and
takes every precaution to provide you with the highest level of privacy
within our online store.
Collection and Use of Personal Information
The collection of personal information
online is designed to protect access to your personal accounts and to assist
us in providing you with the products and services you want and need. All
personal information collected and stored by Chick's is used for our specific
business purposes.
Employing stringent security measures in
the collection of your personal information, all Chick's online transactions
are submitted to our secure server through Secure Sockets Layer (SSL),
an encrypted protocol that enables a web browser
and a web server to communicate securely.
We collect personal information not only to fulfill your order, but also to make our services more rewarding for you to use. We use this information for internal purposes, such as studying our customers' preferences and improving the customer experience. We may also use your contact information to communicate with you for account and promotional purposes.
We do not sell, rent or license any customer personal information.
We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on us.
Limited Employee Access to Personal
Information
Chick's limits employee access to your personal
information to only those administrators with a business reason for knowing
such information. Chick's also educates all employees about the importance
of confidentiality and customer privacy.
Correcting, Updating, and Removing Your Personal Information
You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in those emails, or you can contact us at privacy@chicksaddlery.com. Please note, if you opt-out of receiving our newsletter or marketing emails, you may still receive important administrative communications from us, as long as your account is active, or as needed to provide you services.
To review and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate, or to restrict or request deletion of personal information you have provided to us, please contact us at privacy@chicksaddlery.com. For security purposes, we will only respond to such requests regarding personal information in our database that is associated with the email address you used to send your request, and additional information may be required to verify your identity before doing so.
Please note, we will retain your personal information for as long as your account is active, or as needed to provide you services, including use of our websites and social media pages. If you wish to cancel your account, or request that we no longer use your personal information to provide you services, contact us at privacy@chicksaddlery.com. Following cancellation of your account or processing of your request for us to discontinue providing services to you, we will only retain and use your information as necessary for recordkeeping purposes, and to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
Questions about our Privacy Policy
If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please email or write us at:
Chick's Discount Saddlery
attn: Privacy
18011 South DuPont Highway
Harrington, DE 19952.
United States
privacy@chicksaddlery.com
Copyright © 2020 Chicks Discount Saddlery.
